theretrofitsource.com 2011-11-26

# The Retrofit Source Inc

Our customers' privacy is of the utmost important to us. Accordingly, The Retrofit Source has made it our policy to provide online content that requires only minimal collection of information. Furthermore, to better protect your privacy we issue this notice explaining our online information practices and the way in which you can determine how your information is managed. 

The Retrofit Source only collects personal information from our visitors (1) for the specific purpose for which it is submitted, (2) to improve the content, appearance, or utility of this website, (3) to track our visitors' use of this website, and (4) to notify our visitors of any updates. For instance, we collect information such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, phone, and credit card numbers that you provide when placing an order, when participating in a promotion or survey, or when submitting comments or questions. We do not share your personal information unless you have given us permission to do so. We may obtain from third parties e-mail and postal addresses for select mailings. Sensitive information such as credit card numbers are not stored for your protection. 

The Retrofit Source uses appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to guard our online visitors' personal information against unauthorized access and use. All information is protected by The Retrofit Source's security measures, which are periodically reviewed. 

If you would like us to remove you from our e-mail or postal mailing lists, please contact us and provide your full name, e-mail, and postal address. 

Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifying information from anyone under age 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we receive actual knowledge that a The Retrofit Source subscriber is under age 13, we will remove all personally identifying information about that person from our files. 

The Retrofit Source reserves the right to use cookies to improve our customers' shopping experience, but we do not store personally identifying information in your cookie. While you can turn cookies off in your browner, if you do so we will be unable to track your order and enable you to purchase from this website. 

This website may contain links to other sites, and we make every effort only to link to sites that share our commitment to safeguarding visitors' privacy. Of course, The Retrofit Source is not responsible for the content of or the privacy practices employed by other sites. 

The Retrofit Source may, at our discretion, change modify, amend, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. We encourage you to check our Privacy Policy periodically for any such changes. Any changes to this Privacy Policy are effective on the date that they are posted, and your use of this website following any such changes means that you accept the changes.
